I just want to share my joy that we had a victory today.
I spent last weekend in Montgomery, Alabama with Evan Milligan, Kadida Stone and the Alabama Forward Crew who are working diligently to counteract Alabama's rampant voter suppression.
They've been working so diligently that took Alabama to court.
And in the case of Merrill v. Milligan, the Supreme Court surprisingly ruled in their favor that the voting lines in Alabama have been drawn incorrectly and are violating the Voting Rights Act.
Now, of course, Clarence Thomas wrote like a 55 page dissent, just massa massa in the whole situation.
But more importantly, what this signifies is just how much your vote counts.
Alabama has over 25 percent black people in the state, and they are trying to say that out of the seven districts of Alabama, only one was needed to represent black voters.
Absolutely incorrect.
This ruling also preserves the Voting Rights Act and the reality that the laws made were specifically to make sure that black voters are represented.
Alabama will have to redraw congressional maps.
Now, Louisiana will as well.
And other states possibly will have their laws triggered because of this.
This is a day of celebration.
Let's enjoy it.
Congrats, y'all.